[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Woody Allens black-and-white movie Stardust Memories parodies the 1963 movie 8\u00bd by this European director.", "correct_answer": "Federico Fellini", "incorrect_answers": ["Ingmar Bergman", "Bernardo Bertolucci", "Francois Ozon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the most important buildings in the US - the White House, was gutted in this year.", "correct_answer": "1814", "incorrect_answers": ["1787", "1843", "1912"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the all-time favorite movie Pretty in Pink come out?", "correct_answer": "Feb 1986", "incorrect_answers": ["Dec 1988", "March 1988", "April 1986"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actor who starred as the lawyer in Matlock started out as a real lawyer.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Near the end of the movie 2001 Maniacs, Anderson and Joey jump on Malcolms motorcycle and speed off. They alert the police and find out what?", "correct_answer": "Pleasant Valley is a cemetery.", "incorrect_answers": ["They have traveled back in time to the year 1854.", "Pleasant Valleys mayor is the local sheriff.", "Their friends are waiting for them at the police station."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor was the male lead in The Wild Bunch and also starred in The Bridge on the River Kwai.", "correct_answer": "William Holden", "incorrect_answers": ["William Gargan", "William Holt", "William Berenger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Teams in the NHL and the NBA both usually play this many regular season games.", "correct_answer": "82", "incorrect_answers": ["104", "55", "96"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many children do Miranda and Daniel have in the movie Mrs. Doubtfire?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "5", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character in the movie American Pie started her stories with this one time at band camp?", "correct_answer": "Michele", "incorrect_answers": ["Nadia", "Heather", "Vicky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Dax Shepards middle name?", "correct_answer": "Randall", "incorrect_answers": ["Max", "Lance", "Dustin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was Broken Arrow a black-and-white movie?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Manatees range in weight from 900 to 1200 pounds (400-550 kg.)", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]